data =
    '[{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "A tool for visualising of simple tabular data via charts and graphs", "answer" : "Spreadsheets"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "This tool is used to report, organize, alter and display data", "answer" : "Reporting Software"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "This stage of business intelligence is about the identification, evaluation of actions might be taken at different times", "answer" : "Risk Management"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "How many key stages are in business intelligence", "answer" : "Five"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "A process of protecting data from external attacks and data corruption", "answer" : "Data Security"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "In this process of BI, analysts explore data through visualization", "answer" : "Visual Analytics"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "A process of interpreting large data sets into graphs", "answer" : "Data Visualization"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "A management reporting tool to measure how well the organization company is performing", "answer" : "Dashboards" },' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "The discovery, interpretation and communication of meaningful patterns in data", "answer" : "Analytics"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "A set of data that gives information about some data", "answer" : "Metadata"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "A BI role who is responsible for designing the initial reporting templates and dashboards in the front-end applications", "answer" : "BI Application Designer"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "A system that enables users to create, read, update and delete data in a database", "answer" : "Database Management System"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "A process of defining, analysing and structuring data within data", "answer" : "Data Modelling"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "A data structure that stores values for a specific column in a table", "answer" : "Index"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "An arrangement of tables in a database such that the model resembles a snowflake shape", "answer" : "Snowflake Schema"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "This portion of a program usually interfaces directly with the end user", "answer" : "Front-end"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "A large store of data accumulated from a wide range of sources that can be processed within a company", "answer" : "Data Warehouse"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "A role that is responsible for directing a database and maintaining the data safe", "answer" : "Database Administrator"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "A style of data mart schema and most widely used approach to develop data warehouses", "answer" : "Star Schema"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A process that organizes large business databases and supports complex analysis", "answer" : "Online Analytical processing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A way of storing data in a multidimensional form, generally for reporting purposes", "answer" : "OLAP Cube"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A method of reading and updating all records in a data source during warehouse loading. It is one of the two techniques of loading data", "answer" : "Full Load"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A graphical representation of the progress over time of users, toward some specified goal and highlighting them", "answer" : "Scoreboard"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "It is a term that refers data dimensions that can change slowly and unpredictably rather than on a static or fixed schedule", "answer" : "Slowly Changing Dimensions"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "It is a term that refers one or more fields in a database table that contain same value in a related table", "answer" : "Table Relations"}]';